[Music]
what I found particularly helpful was
arriving here and it being mostly
strangers and by the end of the weekend
we're able to offer each other insights
that are deeply powerful and very
insightful that not just make me feel
good at the moment but I can take away
in harness in my everyday life it's not
teaching somebody a set of ideas it's
enabling people to feel what it actually
feels like to be a man and in doing that
honoring what it is to be a man and also
the love from contributions from women
as well so I think it's really important
this kind of work exists right now I
truly believe that men need the support
of other men to heal certain things in
themselves and to get a sense of
brotherhood and connection with other
men to learn how to be a man and very
few of us got this from our fathers so
being able to give this to each other in
a space like this is really valuable
every man should do this you know
like there's not enough good positive
role models and information for men
there educates men on how to be better
men and we all need them as a species
there is a real act of courage require
to fully show up and tell the truth to
other men and you know for me doesn't
come naturally necessarily to give that
level of trust but the more the space
builds and the more the trust builds
within the group the easier that becomes
and then the feeling is one not just of
release but one of dignity and strength
and being kind of fully in my power I
felt freedom to just let go and not hold
back and that was really liberating and
also just makes you see how everyday you
go and make yourself small and you
compromise and you don't step fully into
your potential and that that was
something I really felt in that room I'm
getting a glimpse of hey what if you
just dared it was incredibly
constructive it you know things I am a
father
I intend to pass lots of these teachings
to my son I think there's lots of stuff
to have done today that will make me a
better man I believe that in spaces like
this we really get to feel those
masculine energies the fires the
vulnerability whatever but in a space of
understanding that no actually this is a
beautiful gift you know it's something
something to be trusted
something the world really really needs
you never knew that you were missing
this but you are you you don't know that
this is what you've actually wanted your
entire life but it is for our upcoming
events check the rebel wisdom website
[Music]
you